http://www.vajacases.com/pages/privacy-and-policies

Notebooks
MacBook Pro 16"
MacBook Air 13"
MacBook Pro Touch Bar 13"
MacBook Pro Touch Bar 15"
iPad Air - 2020
iPad Pro 12.9"
iPad Pro 11" -
2018-2020
iPad 9.7"
Notebooks
MacBook Pro 16"
MacBook Pro Touch Bar 13"
MacBook Pro Touch Bar 15"
Notebooks
MacBook Pro 16"
MacBook Air 13"
MacBook Pro Touch Bar 13"
MacBook Pro Touch Bar 15"
iPad Air - 2020
iPad Pro 12.9"
iPad Pro 11" -
2018-2020
iPad 9.7"
Notebooks
MacBook Pro 16"
MacBook Pro Touch Bar 13"
MacBook Pro Touch Bar 15"
Offers
Shipping To:
Vaja Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit or make a purchase from vajacases.com (the “Site”).
By using the Services, you consent to the collection, use, retention, and disclosure of your Personal Data for processing as described in, and subject to the limitations set out in, this Privacy Statement.
Note to Residents of the European Union: In order to comply with the requirements of the European General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) for our European users, this Privacy Statement outlines the legal basis on which we process your Personal Data and provides other information required by the GDPR.
PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT
When you visit the Site, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the Site, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the Site, and information about how you interact with the Site. We refer to this automatically-collected information as “Device Information.”
We collect Device Information using the following technologies:
“Cookies” are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org.
“Log files” track actions occurring on the Site, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps.
“Web beacons,” “tags,” and “pixels” are electronic files used to record information about how you browse the Site.
Additionally, when you make a purchase or attempt to make a purchase through the Site, we collect certain information from you, including your name, billing address, shipping address, email address, and phone number. We refer to this information as “Order Information.”
We don´t retain your payment information. This information is only in your bank system and is encrypted during all the process. If you choose a direct payment gateway to complete your purchase, then Shopify stores your credit card data. It is encrypted through the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI-DSS). Your purchase transaction data is stored only as long as is necessary to complete your purchase transaction. After that is complete, your purchase transaction information is deleted. All direct payment gateways adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, MasterCard, American Express and Discover.
PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the secure handling of credit card information by our store and its service providers. For more insight, you may also want to read Shopify’s Terms of Service (https://www.shopify.com/legal/terms) or Privacy Statement (https://www.shopify.com/legal/privacy).
Any parts of payment information, in any of the stages, is shared with third parties. When we talk about “Personal Information” in this Privacy Policy, we are talking both about Device Information and Order Information.
HOW DO WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
Personal Data is any information that would identify a person directly, or indirectly in combination with data from other sources. For example, a full name, home or work address, phone number, national identification number (SSN, SIN, etc.), email address, banking details, IP address, biometric data, usage data, or any information that may individually identify a person.
Vaja may collect Personal Data including without limitation your name, shipping and billing addresses, phone number, email address, payment information, IP address, and device identifiers and/or geolocation information, in the course of its Services, and may use or disclose that Personal Data as described with this Privacy Statement.
We use the Order Information that we collect generally to fulfill any orders placed through the Site (including processing your payment, arranging for shipping, and providing you with invoices and/or order confirmations). Additionally, we use this Order Information to:
Communicate with you; Screen our orders for potential risk or fraud; and When in line with the preferences you have shared with us, provide you with information or advertising relating to our products or services.
We use the Device Information that we collect to help us screen for potential risk and fraud (in particular, your IP address), and more generally to improve and optimize our Site (for example, by generating analytics about how our customers browse and interact with the Site, and to assess the success of our marketing and advertising campaigns, including retargeting).
We also profile our database but use the pseudonymization process to send you advertising about our products.
Profiling means any form of automated processing of personal data consisting of the use of personal data to evaluate certain personal aspects relating to a natural person, in particular, to analyze or predict aspects concerning that natural person's performance at work, health, personal preferences, interests, reliability, behavior, location or movements.
Pseudonymization is the processing of personal data in such a manner that the personal data can no longer be attributed to a specific data subject without the use of additional information, provided that such additional information is kept separately and is subject to technical and organisational measures to ensure that the personal data are not attributed to an identified or identifiable natural person.
SHARING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION
We share your Personal Information with third parties to help us use your Personal Information, as described above. For example, we use Shopify to power our online store--you can read more about how Shopify uses your Personal Information here: https://www.shopify.com/legal/privacy. We also use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use the Site--you can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here: https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy. You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.
Finally, we may also share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or another lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights.
BEHAVIORAL ADVERTISING
As described above, we use your Personal Information to provide you with targeted advertisements or marketing communications we believe may be of interest to you. For more information about how targeted advertising works, you can visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s (“NAI”) educational page at http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work.
You can opt out of targeted advertising by: FACEBOOK https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=ads INSTAGRAM https://help.instagram.com/155833707900388 GOOGLE https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymous BING https://advertise.bingads.microsoft.com/en-us/resources/policies/personalized-ads
Additionally, you can opt out of some of these services by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out portal at http://optout.aboutads.info.
DO NOT TRACK
Please note that we do not alter our Site’s data collection and use practices when we see a Do Not Track signal from your browser.
YOUR RIGHTS
If you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information is corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below.
Additionally, if you are a European resident we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example if you make an order through the Site), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above. Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to Canada and the United States.
DATA RETENTION
When you place an order through the Site, we will maintain your Order Information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information. Any time you ask, your data will be deleted, but the records will be anonymized.
CHANGES
We may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons.
CONTACT US
For more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact us by e-mail at support@vajacases.com or by mail using the details provided below:
Vajacases [Re: Privacy Compliance Officer] 12309 sw 132nd ct Miami Florida US 33186
POLICIES
Warranty Policy
At Vaja, we do our best to make goods that you can use daily, and that you can also enjoy for a long time. We totally understand that your leather good will be riding with you almost 24/7, jumping from your hands to your pocket or bag, again back to your hands and so on and so forth. And it is because we know that our products have to put up with these daily hazards that we only use the best of the best materials available! We encourage you to take special care of your extraordinary Vaja goods, to treasure them as you do with your best pair of shoes. As you know using the same pair of shoes everyday will wear them down faster, so do show them some love, remember that they may need a small repair or clean now and then.
On the other hand, we are also part human being (Yeap! Bet you didn’t see that coming!), thus we are not entirely perfect. If you are one of those unfortunate ones who received a faulty product with an unintended manufacturing defect, or even if something breaks within an immediate 6 month period after your purchase, please contact us immediately via support@vajacases.com, so we can determine what happened and get back to you with a suitable solution.
Warranty repairs
We offer warranty repairs on almost all our products. But again, if you are one of the unfortunate who need a small repair in your Vaja goods within the 6 month warranty period, please email us at support@vajacases.com.
Please bear in mind that repairs are carried out at our main factory in Argentina, which means that once we receive the product back from you, it will take something between 2-4 weeks to repair it depending on the issue. Sometimes, it all comes down to a simple stitching repair which can be done at your local leather repair store.
From time to time, we may regret to get back to you explaining that due to the vast color and leather selection offered under our customizable goods section, we might not have the exact same leather/color available to make the repair, and that we may need to use a slightly different color.
Repairs Outside Warranty
If something breaks outside the 6 month warranty period, don’t panic! We also offer repair services. If you think the repair needs our specialists, please contact us at support@vajacases.com with pictures of the problem and we will send you a quote for the estimated repair and shipping cost. Keep in mind that once we receive the product back, it will take around 4-6 weeks to fully repair it, and that in case the product is over 6 months old, we may have to use a different color/leather/thread/material which may not match your original product 100%. We know that it might be pretty hard to survive without your beloved leather good for a few weeks; sometimes all it needs is just a small simple stitching repair which can be done quickly and easily at a local leather repair shop. If you are wavering about what to do, send us a picture and we will gladly let you know how it can be repaired locally or explain you how to send it on a recreation trip to Buenos Aires.
Returns
Our return policy lasts 30 days. Unfortunately, we can’t offer you a refund or exchange if 30 days have already gone by since the time of your purchase. To be eligible for a return, your item must be unused and in the exact same condition you received it, including its original packaging. Under no circumstance will our liability exceed the amount of the original sale and all returned items must have their corresponding RMA (Return Merchandise Authorization) issued by us to warrant returns. Products damage as result of abuse, misuse, improper repairs/maintenance, installation, or alteration/modification will be VOID of our return policy and warranty. This applies to both, our stock and our custom-designed orders. Our liability does not cover lost or stolen packages which have been mailed back to us under warranty or return. In this case, the customer is the shipper and it will be the only one who may file a lost claim to the shipping company that was involved. As such, any interaction regarding the lost claim must involve the customer and the shipping company.
Custom Fees
A 30% return fee is charged to all custom products which are returned and turn not to be due to a manufacturing defect. Custom orders cancellation, modification or returns: Vaja processes customized products 24 hours after the online order was submitted. Therefore, cancellations for full refunds or modifications to customized online orders are only possible within an immediate-24-hours-window. After this time frame, the production line will be assembling the item; from this moment on the product belongs solely to the customer who ordered it (the customer who ordered the product is the sole owner of the case even if it has not been shipped yet), any cancellation or modification request will incur a cancellation fee according to the time that has passed since the order was placed and it will be charged as follows: first 24hs: free of charge. 1-7 days after purchase: 5% of the product price 8-15 days after purchase : 10% of the product price 15 days onwards after purchase: 20% of the product price After product has been finished or shipped: 30% of the product price.
Only upon extraordinary circumstances may Vaja contemplate a custom case return followed by a card refund; such as material or confection flaws, or product malfunctioning under normal use. In all scenarios customers may be required to submit proving pictures of the faulty product to be analyzed by our Vaja Product Department which will approve and process the corresponding RMA.
Additional non-returnable items:
Gift cards To complete your return, we require receipt or proof of purchase. Please do not send your purchase back to the address from where it was sent. There are certain situations where only partial refunds are granted (if applicable) Products with obvious signs of use, any item that is not in its original condition, which is damaged or missing parts for reasons other than our error, any item that is returned after 30 days of its delivery.
Refunds (if applicable)
Once your return was received and inspected, we will send you an email to notify you that your item is in good hands. We will also send you our approval or rejection of the refund application. If approved, then your refund will be processed, and a credit will automatically be applied to your credit card, or original method of payment, within a certain amount of days.
Late or missing refunds (if applicable)
If you haven’t received your refund yet, please check your bank account again first and then contact your credit card company. It may take a while before the refund is officially posted. Next step, get in touch with your bank. There is often some processing time before a refund is posted. If you went through these steps and you have not received your refund yet, please contact us at support@vajacases.com.
Sale items (if applicable)
Unfortunately sale items cannot be refunded nor returned; only regular priced items are refundable.
Late or missing refunds (if applicable)
If you haven’t received your refund yet, please check your bank account again first and then contact your credit card company. It may take a while before the refund is officially posted. Next step, get in touch with your bank. There is often some processing time before a refund is posted. If you went through these steps and you have not received your refund yet, please contact us at support@vajacases.com.
Exchanges (if applicable)
We only replace items if they are defective or damaged. If you need to exchange it for the same item, send us an email at support@vajacases.com, we will issue RMA # and send you the instructions to ship it to our Returns Warehouse at 13830 SW 127th Ct Miami Florida US 33186.
Gifts
If the item was marked as a gift when purchased and shipped directly to you, you’ll receive gift credit for the value of your return. Once the returned item is received, a gift certificate will be mailed to you. If the item wasn’t marked as a gift when purchased, or the gift-giver had the order shipped to him to give it to you later, we will refund the gift-giver and he or she will find out about your return.
Shipping
Returns should be mailed to: 13830 SW 27th Ct Miami Florida US 33186. In the case of a refund, shipping fees will be deducted from the refund sum directly. Shipping fees are not refundable and shall be borne by the purchaser. The time it takes for an exchanged item to reach your address will depend on where you live. Unfortunately, we cannot guarantee that you will receive the returned item but we encourage you to consider a track package shipping service or to pay for shipping insurance if the value of the item exceeds $75.
Updated on 5/24/2018
Follow
iPhone Leather Cases
Our Leather
Blog
Privacy / Policies
Shipping Policies
Terms of Service
© 2020 Vaja.
US LLC. All rights reserved
Where are you located?
USA
European Union
Global ( rest of the world )
